我们还有别的选择吗
What other options do we have?
要想与'纽核力'抗衡
We need serious funding
我们需要大量资金注入
to go up against Nucleus,
但根本没人愿意投资我们
and we don't have that.
-听着  -我会听的
- So, listen-- - I will listen
听你给我蛋蛋马杀鸡的声音
to the sound of you chortling on my balls.
-得了吧  -理查德
- Okay. - Richard,
我是个自由无拘的生意男
I'm an independent businessman.
重点强调"自由无拘"
Emphasis on "Independent."
还有"生意"
And "Business."
仔细想想的话  还要强调"男"人
And "Man," come to think of it.
别算上我
Count me out.
其实给你的条件并不包括在'互利'任职
Actually, you're not being offered employment at Hooli.
他们准备从你那完全买断
They give you a full buy-out.
开价多高
How big?
可能我解释得还不够清楚
Okay, maybe I'm not explaining this right.
听盖文·贝尔森讲的话
I mean, when you hear Gavin Belson say it,